Reading A Love of Learning Daniel is reading an article about Benjamin Franklin.
Here is the article.
Benjamin Franklin, a lifelong learner.
A writer, scientist, inventor and one of the founding fathers of the United States.
Benjamin Franklin was a man of many talents.
He was also one of the most famous people in the 18th century.
From a young age, Franklin's great love of learning set him apart from many others.
As one of 17 children in a big family, Franklin had only two years of education.
After that, he started working in his brother's print shop.
Franklin stayed up very late in order to return them early the next day.
Curious about the world around him, Franklin once became interested in studying storms.
He followed the storms and did many tests.
Then he found out that storms moved from one place to another.
His findings helped predict the weather.
What's more, Franklin had a great love for science, so his countless inventions came as no surprise.
Even in his late 70s, he invented a type of special glasses to help him see better.
Franklin did not make money from any of his inventions, but let people use them for free.
His greatness goes further than that.
As a lifelong learner, he saw learning as an exciting journey full of wonder and success.
This is his greatest gift to the world.